I don’t know anymore whether the victims
or the murderer that’s more of a sicko.
The crime scene Nekros means
for MP Jaratphong must be…
The temple he built.
Hey! Stop!
Phat. Phat.
Phat!
There’s been a speculation
that each victim in this case,
especially MP Jaratphong,
is involved in some shady businesses
and has severely assaulted
the suspect’s family.
Does the police department think
this is a vigilante act that serves
to make up for the delayed justice?
We investigate based on
the witnesses and evidence.
We do not take into consideration
what the backgrounds of the victims are.
Taking someone’s life
is a crime we do not tolerate.
We will let the laws decide
what is right or wrong.
Are you talking about the same laws
that failed to protect Kim’s family
and caused an innocent child
to grow up to be a murderer?
How can you be certain, sir,
that you can really give him justice,
instead of just silencing someone
who’s wrong to save his humanity?
Our job is to enforce the laws
that keep our society in check.
Bringing up the past
might be a little too complicated
to bring up right now.
Thank you all for your attention.
Sir.
Sir, please answer the questions.
-Sir.
Praew.
He woke up to eat
and just fell back asleep.
Oh, Kaye. I have something to tell you.
Phat opened his eyes
and didn’t even ask about me one bit.
He asked about you.
Should I be offended?
Bye.
What are you doing out there?
What are you getting up for?
Is your wound good enough
to be walking around like this?
Who’d have thought my first days off
would be a long holiday?
Thank you…
for risking your life to save me.
Why are you thanking me?
It was my job as a cop anyway.
At least now you know
there are still some good cops out there.
It’s been a long time…
since I could let my mind
be at peace like this.
Was your previous case just as rough?
This case is… the worst so far.
Honestly…
You…
You didn’t need to save someone like me.
You should have let me pay for what I did
and let me mess it up completely.
If you were gonna mess it up,
I’d love to help you
before you ruin the entire thing.
(It’s been three days)
(since the police took the suspect behind
the Nekros serial murder into custody)
(after tireless investigation
and intense cooperation.)
(We’ll see what is waiting at the end
of the tunnel for this vigilante.)
(This case has tremendously uplifted
the image of the police department)
(which has been subpar for so long.)
(The public is surely
keeping their eyes on this case.)
Your wound’s not completely healed.
Why are you bringing yourself to work?
Worried about me?
I need to get this case closed.
I can’t waste any time.
The press is putting us
under a lot of pressure.
If I let it go on any longer,
it would just cause
a collective anxiety in the public.
What about you?
Are you sure you want to see
that sicko investigated?
Of course.
I think I might be useful.
Alright. Let’s go.
Surprise!
Welcome back to work, Inspector.
We were nearly killed closing this case.
Weren’t we, guys?
Thank you.
Well done, all of you.
But if you’re done celebrating, tidy up.
Our work isn’t over.
Ugh!
Go on. Get back to work.
Get ready to question Kim
so we can get on with his confession.
More importantly,
we need to send this to the prosecutor
as soon as possible
before the press makes even more
of a mess of this case.
-Yes, sir.
Inspector.
Don’t worry about the report.
Our crime lab just sent in the results,
and Kim’s DNA and fingerprints
are all over all the crime scenes.
With this kind of evidence,
there’s no way he’s getting away.
Good work, Nop.
Yes, sir.
(Who is Anan Pratonngam or Kim,)
(the serial murderer
behind the Nekros murders)
(who has just been arrested?)
(Let me take you back in time.)
(Little Kim was crying for justice.)
(He was the only witness)
(when his mother was brutally murdered
and ransacked for her organs.)
(This human trafficking business
was clearcut)
(and directly
involved with MP Jaratphong.)
(But no matter
how obvious the business was,)
(this case still went silent.)
(Kim became a homeless orphan,)
(watching the famous MP
enjoying his time in the spotlight.)
(It raises the question:)
(Is Kim a vicious devil or a victim
of the miscarriage of justice?)
You’re thinking his life is miserable.
That is no excuse to take anyone’s life.
Maybe he just needs his voice to be heard.
And that’s why we need to go
and listen to him with our own ears.
You ready?
I’m going to investigate him now.
I thought you were dead!
(Congrats, sir.)
(What a relief you made it through
so we could have a chat.)
How is your wound?
Nosy bastard.
But well…
You came all this way to see me.
What business, sir?
Just say what you need to say.
Whether or not you confess,
in the end,
you will surrender
in front of the evidence.
How about this, Inspector?
I’ll tell you a story.
You remember that pig?
When I plunged the knife into his skin
and slowly dragged it…
Whoosh!
I took my time filleting him.
Filleting his flabby skin
and threw it in the toilet.
And his voice, sir…
He was wailing like pigs
in a slaughterhouse.
Listen up, sir.
If I listen very closely right now,
I can still hear his voice ringing in my ears.
(Do you think Mr. Kill
would be proud of me, Inspector?)
I did everything exactly like in the manga.
I took the knife
and made an upside down pentagram.
(That’s not all, sir.)
Before I bashed his head open,
I was meticulous in comparing it
to the panels in the manga.
Making sure it’s perfect.
I was aiming and then I smashed!
With the first blow,
his head went like this.
But he didn’t bleed.
So I smashed again, sir!
And that did the job, Inspector.
He was bleeding like…
Hmm.
Kim.
I’ll tell you what.
No one is proud of you.
Oh.
One more thing…
Your beloved prophet?
He’s so disappointed in you.
Because your work sucks so damn bad.
How could he be disappointed?
(How dare you say that to me,
you jerkass Inspector!)
It’s because of cops like you
that the world needs Nekros.
That’s not true. It can’t be true!
Mr. Kill must be proud of me.
I made sure to get all the details.
Go away, you asshole!
Shut your dirty hole, freaking cop.
He doesn’t know anything.
Cops like him don’t know shit.
I suggest you keep your mouth shut
since you’ll have plenty of time
to talk in prison, Kim.
Go away!
It can’t be true!
You don’t know Mr. Kill as well as I do.
(No way!)
(It’s not true.)
(He was just talking nonsense.)
(He was just threatening me.)
Right?
I see you through!
(That was just a threat.)
(I know it.)
Let’s go home.
You’ve been staring at Kim so much
his face might as well
jump out of the screen.
I can’t listen to my parents complain
about my late nights anymore, you know?
You don’t think this is too easy?
Everything seems too perfectly staged.
If you think something’s wrong,
then I guess it is.
Oh, it’s my mom.
I need to go.
I’ll be here early tomorrow to help you.
-See you.
-Get home safe.
Bye.
Oh, you’re still here.
I’m just looking through something.
I’ll go home soon.
Oh, Praew.
Do you know who this person is?
I saw him sticking
to your big brother’s side the whole time.
Okay.
If you’re not comfortable telling me,
it’s alright.
Let’s say you just need to say yes or no.
Alright?
Yes.
I’ve been wondering why your brother…
has a romance manga artist
like K.Cupid as his consultant.
But I was at my wit’s end,
unless Kaye is Mr. Kill.
Am I right?
I guess it’s time Mr. Kill makes
his identity public to his fans.
No need to hold back, guys.
This is my mother’s restaurant.
We can stay till sunrise!
Alright!
Mom, come on.
It’s not every day
we get to celebrate like this.
Am I right?
Inspector is here, Mom.
Mwah, mwah.
Look at how beautiful she is, guys.
Oh, my sweet talker.
Go on and sit down.
You can all make yourselves at home.
If you need anything,
please just let Nop know.
-Thank you, ma’am.
-Thank you.
Have a great time.
Love you, Mom.
Oh, look at you.
You still coddle up to your mama
at this big age?
You don’t look the type!
Don’t make fun of me.
Mr. Chaiwat asks me
to give you this bottle of wine
to celebrate your closing a national case.
I bet you’ll be my boss
within a few years.
I’ll be in your care.
Give my thanks to Uncle Chaiwat.
Inspector, please have a seat.
This is my mother’s restaurant.
I’ll take care of you.
What do you drink?
Wine or beer?
Anything is fine by me.
Alright. Please have a seat.
You must be hungry.
Alright, guys.
Make room.
Here you go.
Here.
Aren’t you hungry?
I can’t really stomach anything.
But thank you.
Here.
The biggest piece for our MVP.
Thank you.
Without Kaye,
we wouldn’t be able to close this case.
You were a big help. Thank you.
Guys, let’s raise our cups for Kaye!
Bottoms up!
Alright.
Come on.
In three, two, one…
Cheers!
Drink up, y’all.
Why did you sneak out
to make that serious face?
What?
I just needed some fresh air.
I was just thinking.
You want a puff?
Thank you.
Work’s done.
Case closed.
Can you stop making a face like
you’re thinking about
having someone arrested?
See? You actually know how to smile.
Because if you don’t,
I’ll start getting stressed out, too.
Here they come!
Mr. Kim, how are you feeling?
Anything to say to the people?
Who hired you?
What was your motivation?
Why did you choose to imitate Nekros?
What is your association with the victims?
Stay still!
Kim!
How does it feel to be praised
for doing something wrong?
What do you think of the fact
people think you’re a hero?
Who hired you?
Do you accept your judgement?
Do you believe justice will be served?
Give us an answer.
It is stuffy inside, isn’t it?
Well…
I have a question.
If Kim wasn’t arrested right now,
who would be the next victim?
Oh, my name is Thun.
Should I call you Kaye…
or Mr. Kill?
Uh…
What do you want?
I just want a short interview with you
as the artist who created Nekros.
I’m sorry.
I’m not available for interviews.
Excuse me.
Mr. Kaye.
If you choose to stay silent,
lies will become truths.
Because the person
who knows the truth like you
chooses to stay silent.
Don’t forget
what your father went through,
and who destroyed your family.
Remember.
What did you have to do
when you created the demon like Nekros?
Hey. What are you doing?
I’m not doing anything wrong, sir.
I’m only speaking the truth.
Or is it wrong in this country
to tell the truth?
And there are so many things…
Kaye doesn’t know, such as…
Your father.
You wanna be on my nerves, huh?
I’m done putting up with it, you jerk!
Make way!
Phat!
you jerk!
Phat, stop!
Inspector!
Stop it!
Do you realize what you just did?
I know I was wrong.
Your job is to enforce laws,
not being a bully.
And the first thing you need
to learn how to do is
how to control your emotions.
Don’t allow anyone to use them
against you like this.
I’m sorry, Uncle.
I promise it won’t happen again.
I got an order of suspension for you,
as well as an order to set up a committee
to investigate your behavior.
The effect is immediate.
I tried to help you, Phat.
But the video of you punching
that reporter is all over the internet.
I really can’t protect you.
Oh, Inspector?
How’s your hand?
It’s… alright.
Dinner?
Do you want to have dinner with me?
I’ll wait downstairs.
Well, you’re suspended.
Are you alright?
I’m okay.
I haven’t had time to rest at all before.
But now that I closed the case,
it feels like a holiday to me.
Don’t you have anywhere you want to go
during your break, then?
You have time?
Why?
Hmm…
Come with me.
Alright. Kick.
It’s for your own good.
You might run into
those debt collectors again.
At least you’ll be able to put up a fight.
Ready?
Huh?
If you’re not ready, this is what you get.
Oh, wow, Inspector.
Is your injury all healed up now?
Maybe. It’s just a throb.
Come on.
Pick up the gun.
Like this?
Yeah.
Keep your arms straight.
Bend forward a little.
Make sure the middle
of the gun is straight.
Alright. Straight.
Put your finger on the trigger.
Okay.
Yeah.
Pull the trigger.
See?
Told you it’s easy.
Yeah.
Your lighter’s no good.
Thanks.
What does sensei mean?
It’s Japanese.
It means ‘teacher.’
Why?
Praew texted me.
I told her I’m with you.
She said, “Say hello to sensei for me.”
Oh.
Well…
Say hello to her for me.
Sure.
Oh, and…
When are you going back to work?
I have an interview on Monday.
I think I might be suspended for a week…
or a month.
I…
I’m sorry.
Stop apologizing.
It’s not your fault.
And honestly…
He had it coming.
If you think about it,
he was trying to pit me and my sister
against each other.
He deserved that.
Oh, and if you wonder if I’m sorry…
I’m not.
Phat.
Hmm?
Do you think Nekros…
really is Kim?
Us police officers don’t get to decide
based on our gut feelings.
Kim confessed.
And all the evidence
pointed to him as Nekros.
Kaye.
Hmm?
Everything's over now.
You need to move on as well.
And don’t look back.
Sure thing.
I don’t plan to write
any more chapters for Nekros.
MAILBOX (NO TITLE)
CONTACT ME BACK.
CONTACT ME BACK. FROM MR. KILL.
SEND
I ruined everything at the end, Prim.
(Come on.)
(Even if you didn’t tell him,
Thun would have found out anyway.)
(What we need to focus on right now)
(is the scoop for Kim
we’ve been assigned.)
(I heard Thun tell the team today)
(that Kim doesn’t let
his relatives or reporters in.)
(So it’s hopeless
to get an interview with him.)
Prim, I think there’s still hope.
I have to go.
Bye.
(Bye.)
Hello.
(Hello, Praew.)
Sorry to bother you so late.
(Did you…)
Did you know I got all the information
for Nekros from my fans on my blog?
Is that why there’s a tiny watermark
of the username on the cover?
Yes.
I found something strange.
Every chapter of Nekros
that the crimes were based on…
is from the same user.
The name is…
Asura.
I’ve been trying to contact Asura.
But there’s no answer.
Now I want to know…
if there’s any more chapters of Nekros
with Asura’s contribution.
You want to find
the missing Nekros files, is that it?
(Yes.)
I’ll help you.
Thank you.
It’s alright.
I need a favor as well.
What is it?
Don’t worry about Asura.
I posted something in the Nekros fan blog.
I’m sure someone has those old files.
I’ll hurry home and check.
Honestly I’m not worried about that.
I’m more worried about
what we’re doing right now.
If Phat finds out,
he’s going to be so mad at us.
Are you Mr. Chankacha?
Yes.
The inmate agrees to see
you and your friend.
Please come in.
I’m really happy you came to see me.
I want to ask you about
your motivations for murders—
I’m not talking to you.
He’s the only person I’ll talk to.
Well…
I’ll ask you honestly.
You didn’t do it alone, did you?
Faith.
Everything Nekros did…
I did it all.
Are you proud of me?
You are, aren’t you?
Do you know Asura?
I want to know how you chose
which chapter to imitate,
and when you killed them…
Who helped you come up with the methods?
I…
I’m just a spark of fire.
Floating…
Floating.
Igniting the fire with no doubt.
I’m just the messenger.
A fire that’s started blazing
won’t be so easy to put out.
Let’s go.
Time’s up.
Inspector.
Where are the old files?
I looked for them like you asked me to.
But…
What a coincidence.
Are you also looking for the files
for the Thai Investment Bank case?
Yes.
There’s something
I’d like to cross-reference.
But if you’re working on it,
I’ll have Nop come back for them later.
Inspector.
You need to take better care
of your sister and Mr. Kaye.
I got a report
that Mr. Kaye and your sister
asked to visit Kim in prison today.
And one more thing…
I heard Mr. Kaye was initially
the prime suspect in this case.
I’m worried about you.
I don’t want this to blow up.
The case is closed.
The public is satisfied.
The higher-ups are happy.
Let’s not dig up the mess again.
Praew, listen to me.
We need to tell Phat about this.
But if we do, he’s going to be so mad.
But this is a matter of life and death.
If it’s really Chapter 20,
Phat needs to know.
He’ll stop the murderer in time.
We need to tell him.
Why did you two show up at the prison?
Huh?
Phat, listen.
First of all, I’m sorry.
But I needed to go because
I received some new information.
It got me thinking
that the person who doesn’t want
this nonsense to end…
is you.
You want people to keep dying
as sacrifices for your psychotic manga.
Am I right?
Phat.
We were just looking for the truth.
Don’t take your frustration out on Kaye.
You need to keep quiet.
You’re just his fan.
You’re only too willing to let him
mess with your head
and be used like a tool.
You’re not a cop or a reporter.
What you are is just a brat!
Yeah!
I’m just a useless thing to you.
You don’t believe in me at all.
(Good evening.)
(For our special scoop today,)
(we bring you the story of another person
everyone’s been anticipating.)
(The man who left a bruise on my face.)
(Inspector Yotsaphat Traikanawut.)
(I’m sure many are familiar
with his surname.)
(He’s the nephew
of the famous Commissioner Chaiwat.)
(However, this was also the surname
of Commissioner Praphaphat,)
(the Inspector’s very own father,)
(the cop accused of taking bribes
to destroy the evidence regarding)
(the Thai Investment Bank case,)
(allowing the investors to walk free
while the grassroot people took the blame.)
(The very reason many families
lost everything they had,)
(and chose to end their own lives
to escape their problems.)
(The number you have dialed
cannot be connected at the moment.)
You knew all this time, didn’t you?
Your father destroyed my family.
You can hate my father.
You can hate me.
I’ll get it.
But I hate what he did
a hundred times more than you do.
But does that hatred bring him back
to life and put him in jail?
Does it make your father better?
When did you know about my father?
Did you stalk me?
Dad.
I’m sorry I’ve been away for so many days.
How are you doing, Dad?
Are you well?
Did you have dinner?
Let’s get you cleaned up, shall we?
I know what you’re trying to hide.
I understand.
Because if I were you,
I wouldn’t be able to put up with it.
The reason I chose to be a cop
was because I wanted to remind myself
that I would never make
the same mistake my father did.
But you…
Did you ever choose to do anything
besides being stuck in the past?
Thank you for coming with me.
Are you sure about this, Praew?
I mean…
I can tell from out here
that they’re not good people.
The police thought this case
was over with Kim.
But if we gather information
and prove that it’s not over…
I think it’s worth the risk.
Let’s do it.
Let’s go.
First of all,
you need to stop being scared.
Let your body navigate the flow.
When the opponent has an opening,
elbow him with everything you have.
See clearly.
Don’t look away.
If you do,
you won’t see your enemy.
Focus on the opponent in front of you.
Twist your hips.
The number 20 Kim wrote on the glass
must be the clue for the next victim.
There’s a type of murderer
called Mastermind.
He controls everything.
Praew!
I understand what it feels like
for a big brother
to be powerless in saving his sister.
You’re doing your best as a brother.
Your visit that day was the last words
he needed before he killed himself
and erased all traces back to you.
Every cop in the world would think that.
What about you?
Do you still think I’m the murderer?